快点  呆瓜们
Let's hurry it up, fishies.
我们现在毫无防备
We got our pants down out here.
也就只有一打吧
It's only like a dozen.
-我是说  -哈克
- Yeah, I mean -- - Huck.
撤掉托德维修站的工作
Relieve Todd at the maintenance station.
-玛拉  -闭嘴
- Hey, Mara -- - Shut up.
把枪给我
Give me your gun.
感觉怎么样
How's that feel?
-感觉...  -闭嘴
- It, uh, feels -- - Shut up.
去里面拿冷却器  开始打包
Go inside. Get the coolers. Start packing up.
天才
Hey, genius.
抱歉
Sorry.
快去
Go.
小罗伊
Little Roy.
小罗伊  我是玛拉  收到了吗
Little Roy, it's Mara. You copy?
J-Top  我是玛拉  收到了吗
J-Top, it's Mara. You copy?
托德
Todd?
怎么了
Yeah?
封锁每一层楼梯井
Lock the stairwell, every floor.
为什么
Why?
《行尸走肉》
似乎他们修了一道缓冲区
Looks like ?they made themselves a moat.
这也不奇怪  考虑到之前的事
I guess we shouldn't be surprised, considering.
我们能做到的  我们做到过
We can do this. We did before.
对  我就是考虑到这个
Yeah. That's what I was considering.
我之前没在
I wasn't here before.
只需要视野清楚  对吗  戴安
Just need a clear shot. Right, Dianne?
几秒钟就够了
Just a few seconds.
我们只需把握好时机
So we just need to time it right.
假如他们看到我们  开枪  我们就进不去了
They see us, they fire a gun, we're not getting in.
别让他们开枪  戴安
Don't let them fire a gun, Dianne.
摩根  需要我们掩护你吗
Morgan, do you need us to cover you or something?
不需要
I do not.
我们是来帮忙的  不该让你一个人上
Hey, we're here to help. It shouldn't just be you.
我死不了
I don't die.
陛下
Your Majesty!
他在哪
Where is he?
找到国王
Find the King!
行尸围过来了
The damned are upon us!
保护国王
Protect the King!
先保护好你们自己
Protect yourselves!
有人看到他去哪了吗
Anyone see where he went?
他看见我们了
He saw us.
假如他通风报信  那我们就没机会了
If he tells them we're here, it's over before it started.
还有机会  他不会报信的
It is not, and he won't,
因为我们会一起找到他  消灭他
for we together will find him, end him,
然后实现我们最初的承诺
and fulfill the promise of what we have begun.
要相信国王
Trust the King.
哨站在正北方  穿过林子就到
Outpost is due north, through the woods.
他一定会往那边走  所以我们也跟过去
As that's surely his course, so shall it be ours.
假如我们的同志已经到了
If our comrades had already arrived,
他们也会在那里
they'd have been here.
返回集结区
Return to the staging area.
等其他人到了就把大家集合起来
Gather the others when they land.
假如他们还没到
And if they haven't yet,
就把希瓦从笼子里放出来
release Shiva from her cage.
正北方  我们会给你留下标记
Due north. ?We'll leave a trail for you.
要确保这附近没有敌人
Ensure no enemies remain in these environs,
不要落下超过10分钟  去吧
and be not 10 minutes behind. Go.
前进
Onward!
冲向敌人  冲向他的基地
To our foe, then to his compound,
冲向注定的胜利
then to certain victory.
散开  盯住缺口
Spread out! Watch for breaches!
围着他们打  他们麻烦比我们大
We keep 'em locked in, they got bigger problems than us.
我能听到枪声
I can hear the shooting.
原地待命  别出声
Stay where you are. Do not say another word.
如果枪在里面就给个信号  我们马上过来
You signal ?if they're already inside. We'll be there.
走吧  把枪找出来
Come on. Let's find them guns.
迪诺  帮我们开路
Dino, we need an opening.
找条路或者杀条路出来
Find one or make one.
搞什么
What the hell?
0.50勃朗宁重机枪  存放在谢泼德办公室广场
房顶破损  楼顶无看守
四层楼  白天通常没人  车辆20+
进入楼梯  电梯井
这一层没有
Ain't on this floor.
看来只能上楼
Only option is up.
高点  好掩护
High ground. Good cover.
是啊  换我也会放上面
Yeah, I'd put them up there, too.
楼梯
Stairs.
他们胆小  不敢逼近
They're too chickenshit to move in on us.
反打回去  上
We push them back! Go!
右前方有敌人过来
We got some coming up on my right.
压制他们  别让他们过来
Stay on them! Don't let them through!
困住他们  自然都跑不了
We pin them in, it takes care of itself!
按原计划来
That's the plan!
托宾  上
Tobin, move in!
我能搞定  掩护我
I can take them! Cover me!
不  跟托宾一起
No! Wait for Tobin!
没时间了
There's no time!
上  我帮你打掩护
Go! I'll help cover you!
最后一层了
Last floor.
枪一定藏在这里
The guns have gotta be up here.
他说枪在这里
He said they'd be here.
他之前给你的情报都是对的
Everything else he passed you is checking out.
那家伙就是个混蛋
That guy's a piece of shit.
如果那些枪被送到救世堂
Those guns get to the Sanctuary,
就可以突破行尸  辟出通路
they could cut through those walkers and free up an exit.
我们分头行动更快
We'll go faster if we split up.
不管谁找到M2重机枪
I find the M2s, ?you find 'em, we use them,
直接用它支援院子
hit the courtyard right then and there.
快点了结吧
End this quick.
求你  求你别杀我
Aah! Please! Please don't shoot me!
该死  别杀我
Shit. Please don't shoot me.
求你们了  不要
Please don't...
快看  你尿裤了
Oh, look, you pissed your pants.
我不是他们的人
I-I'm not one of them.
我叫迪恩
Uh, m-my name's Dean.
那你怎么还活着
Why are you still talking?
塔拉  等等
Tara, wait.
-稍等  -为什么
- Just wait. ?- For what?
他已经投降了  塔拉
He has his hands up, Tara.
我们有任务
We have a job to do.
你想去查看一下吗
You want to go check that out?
另一队人生死不明
We're missing some people from the other team.
摩根
Morgan?
出来
Come out.
别出来
Just stay in there.
我们正在对攻
We're on top of each other here.
安全之后  我们给你信号
We'll signal you when it's clear.
做好准备
Just be ready.
我来解决  耶稣  让开
I got it, Jesus. Step aside.
塔拉
Tara.
外面正在战斗
There's a firefight outside.
我们连摩根是否活着都不知道
We don't even know if Morgan's alive.
求你了  女士  我不是他们的人
Please, lady. I'm not one of them.
你在这里  手里有枪  你是他们的人
You're here. You had a gun. You are one of them.
我不是  我不是  你要相信我
I'm not. I'm not. You got to believe me.
那你在这里干什么
Then what are you doing here?
我只是一个劳工
I'm just a worker.
他们把我从救世堂带到这里做饭打扫
They brought me from the Sanctuary to cook, clean, whatever.
我别无选择
They did not give me a choice.
他们逼我离开了妻儿
They made me leave my wife and kids.
你们也这么对救世堂里的人吗
Your people do this to the Sanctuary, too?
我的家人还好吗
The families okay?
我们不想伤害劳工
We don't want to hurt the workers.
-我们不会的  -你相信他吗
- We're not going to. - You believe him?
这和他没关系
It's not about him.
我不会朝一个已经举手投降的人开枪
I'm not gonna shoot someone with their hands up,
我也不会让你开枪
and I'm not letting you.
这些药物补给
These medical supplies --
都是山顶寨的吧
they're the Hilltop's, right?
玛姬的孕期维生素
Maggie's prenatals.
他们随心所欲地抢走
They took them because they could,
因为他们根本不在乎
because they don't give a shit.
那我们为什么要在乎
So why should we?
我知道他们杀了你
I know they killed your girlfriend...
-耶稣...  -深爱的女友
- Jesus -- - ...that you loved her.
-你不是这样的人  -现在是
- This isn't you. - ?It is now.
我们不是来复仇的
We're not here for revenge.
-不能变成那样  -可以的
- It can't be about that. - It can.
换我可不会开枪
I wouldn't.
你知道有意思的是什么吗
You know what's funny?
一般我会求你大发慈悲  而不是求帅哥
Normally I'd peg you as the softie, not pretty boy.
你知道故意尿到裤子上有多难吗
You know how hard it is to piss yourself on purpose?
就像是你的老二知道你穿着裤子
It's like your dick knows you're wearing pants.
天  快看
Hell, look that.
这东西是废了
Well, that shit is ruined.
看样子那个蠢婊子玛姬和她孩子
Well, looks like that dumb bitch Maggie and her kid
横竖都要死了
are just gonna die, anyway,
-就跟你俩一样  -我会杀了你
- Just like you two. - I'm gonna kill you.
亲爱的  你杀不了
Oh, honey, no, you're not.
那也会有别人动手  我们有很多人
Then someone else will. There's too many of us.
看  我有不同看法
See, that's where we differ.
如果我带着你俩
If I take the two of you with me,
那我就有了完美保险
then I've got one hell of an insurance policy.
所以你何不放下枪
So why don't you put that thing down
除非你想射穿这个小帅哥
unless you're gonna shoot through this beautiful man here.
我不会问第二遍
I'm not gonna ask you again.
-我觉得她会开枪的  -我会的
- I think she's gonna shoot you. - I am.
是  她会开枪的
Yeah. She is.
闭嘴
Shut up!
-塔拉  -我能做到
- Tara. - I can do it.
塔拉  他拿枪顶着我头
Tara, he has a gun to my head.
马上就不会了
Not for long.
等等  等等  等一下
Wait. Wait. Wait a second.
-去死吧  -好  所以说
- Go to hell. ?- Okay. So ...
你是真想孤注一掷是吗
you really wanna risk it, huh?
为我危及他
Me for him?
我可以现在告诉你  我不值得你这样做
Well, I can tell you right now that I am not worth it.
我们能想法子和解的
We can work this out.
我可能说话爱逞威风装硬汉
I-I may talk a big game like I'm a tough guy,
但我不是
but I'm not.
我只是想...
I really just want to...
你不会下手的
You're not gonna do it.
你下不了手
Not you.
这不是复仇  而是完成任务
It's not about revenge. It's about getting it done.
你在干什么
What the hell are you doing?
他想杀了我们
He tried to kill us.
我跟你讲过了  这和他没关系
I told you -- it's not about him.
所以他就能活着
So he gets to live?
那亚伯拉罕呢  格伦呢  丹妮斯呢
What about Abraham? Glenn? Denise?
这是两码事
This is different.
你不是瑞克  你也不是玛姬
You're not Rick. You're not Maggie.
没错
No.
但她会听我讲我的理由
But she'll hear what I have to say.
撤离一号站  撤离一号站
Evac Sat 1! Evac Sat 1!
耶稣  塔拉
Jesus! Tara!
他们在撤退
They're falling back!
走  走  走
Go! Go! Go!
还有别的路能出去吗
There another way out of here?
有  跟我走
Yeah. Follow my lead.
-托宾  -我没事
- Tobin! - I'm okay!
你们继续  我没事
Just keep going! I'm okay!
他们并不需要逼近我们
They didn't have to move in on us.
糟了
Shit.
在前面
Up ahead.
我看到了
I see it.
我来
This is me.
这家伙怎么成这样了
What befell this creature?
我是说在你下手之前
I mean before you.
现在没时间纠结这些了
We don't have time to figure that out.
离基地不远了
Compound's not far off.
要是他抵达了
If he made it,
要是他们知道我们要来  他们就会有所准备
if they know we're coming, they're gonna be ready.
两种可能  一个事实
Two possibilities, just one fact.
什么事实
And what's that?
不管怎样  我们都要准备好应战
We shall be ready regardless.
我们接下来要面对的
What's about to happen,
不只是几个行尸
it's not just a few walkers.
你知道的吧
You know that, right?
是的  但我依然在笑
Yes. And yet I smile.
为什么
Why?
我心中充满了自信吗
Do I feel the supreme confidence?
还是说我的命运  我的职责
Or is my lot, my job,
需要我表现出这种确定性
to simply project such certainty?
不是也是
No and yes.
是也不是
Yes and no.
最终二者都是
And then finally yes to both.
假装能成  直到真成  宝贝
Fake it till you make it, baby.
我就是这样做到的  也是我正在做的
That's what I've done and what I do.
我之所以是国王  是因为我照亮了一束光
I am King because ?I-I have provided a light
引领我的人民穿过黑暗
to lead my people forward through the darkness,
他们让我的想象成为了现实
and they have made my fictions realities.
所以  这一切和发生过的一切...
So, with all this and everything that's happened --
我们可能都活不下来
All of us may not make it.
我们甚至可能赢不了
We may not even win.
但我依然在笑
And yet I smile.
今天不能畏惧失败
There will be no fantasies of failure this day.
伙计们  这是行尸的血吗
Hey, guys. Is this blood from the wasted?
不是
No.
我们刚才交火时有人打中他了
One of us hit him when we fired on him.
也就是说他走得很慢
Means he's moving slow.
没错
Hells yeah.
依然有希望
We're back in business.
干得漂亮  丹尼尔
Well done, Daniel.
大家都干得漂亮
Well done to us all.
我们继续前进...
We move forward...
推动整个世界一起前进
as we move the very world forward.
那些M2重机枪在哪里
The M2s. Where are they?
这里...没有枪
No...Guns!
格蕾丝
Grace--
在里面吗
They're in there?
不  不要
No! No!
你确定我们能取胜吗
You sure we can do it?
能打败他们吗
We can beat 'em?
凭我们做过的事  积累的经验
What this group has done, what we've learned,
学到的本领  齐心协力  我确定可以
what we've become, all of us -- yes, I'm sure.
把门围起来  包围圈大一点  至少六米
Circle the door, wide, at least 20 feet.
举起枪  但不要开火
Guns up, but hold your fire.
什么
What?
他们会投降的
They're gonna give up.
他们先开火  我们再回击
We only fire if they fire first.
他们先开火  我们会死人的
They fire first, one of us dies.
那我们最好祈祷  他们不开枪
Then let's hope, for my sake, that they don't.
你可以试试阻止我
You can try to stop me.
快点  走  快点
Come on! Go! Move!
放下武器
Drop your weapon!
放下武器  立刻投降
Drop your weapon and surrender.
我挺想活着的
Living sounds good to me.
我们被包围了
We're surrounded.
他们觉得我们蠢  你们别真犯蠢
Don't be as dumb as they think we are.
把枪放下
Put your guns down.
行
It's okay.
我们用麻烦的方法来
We can do it the hard way.
因为就算玛姬听你的
Because even if Maggie listens to you,
瑞克也会听我的
Rick will listen to me.
我们要先下手为强
We have to come for them before they come for us.
不能留活口
We can't leave them alive.
有生命的地方  就有希望
Where there's life, there's possibility.
被他们攻击的希望
Of them hitting us.
靠  我认识你
Shit. I know you.
你也被调过来了吗
You get transferred, too?
摩根
Morgan!
把枪放下
Lower your gun.
我们是来杀他们的
We came here to kill them.
我们应该杀的
We're supposed to.
他们已经投降了
They surrendered.
我们不是这种人
It's not what we do.
那我们是哪种人
Then what do we do, huh?
格雷西
Gracie.
不
No.
那边
That way.
那里
There!
省点子弹  卡罗尔
Save your munitions, Carol.
我们的朋友来了
Our friends have arrived.
弗朗辛
Francine!
你没事吧  你没事吧
You okay? You okay?
我没事  但我们的人需要...
I'm fine, but our people...they need...
天啊  不要
Oh, God. No.
不不不  不要啊
No, no, no, no, no, no.
不要  埃里克  埃里克
No, no. Eric, Eric.
埃里克
Eric.
我们走
Let's go.
这就是我们注定的胜利
And there it is -- our certain victory.
我不因他的死而高兴
This -- I am not glad for his death.
或任何人的死
For anyone's.
我知道
I know.
尼尔逊  我们出动了  采取积极措施
Nelson, we're on the move, taking active measures.
躲起来  止好血
Just hole up, keep it elevated,
如果你看到我们  记得避开枪火
and if you see us, stay out of the line of fire.
被发现了  只能撤了
Jig's up. Gonna have to break chocks.
不
No.
这段旅程不能以失败告终
This journey will not end in retreat.
但他们知道我们要来
But they know we're coming.
他们确实知道
Indeed they do.
该死
Damn it.
手别动
Keep your hands down.
慢慢转身
Turn around slow.
你好  瑞克
Hi, Rick.
你的名字
Your name...
叫莫拉莱斯
is Morales.
亚特兰大营地幸存者之一
在第一季中没有选择前往疾控中心
而是带家人去了伯明翰  后再无音讯
你当时在亚特兰大
You were in Atlanta.
那是很久以前的事了
That was a long time ago.
结束了  瑞克
It's over, Rick.
我呼叫了救世军
I called the Saviors back.
他们正在来的路上
And they're coming.